Within hypervisors, we have virtual machines.
Virtual machines are software-based, fully
functional instances of an operating system
inside a hypervisor, allowing us to run multiple
operating systems in one.
Just for an example, I have two virtual machines
here: one Linux and one Windows.
Each serves a specific purpose.
The Linux virtual machine is here so that
I do not need a separate machine to run Linux.
This instance of Windows is a test machine
that I can use to test things without running
tests on my regular operating system.
That is another reason for having a virtual:
to have a place to test apps and features
without risking one's regular operating system.